touchngo.com.my 2016-05-05

# Touch 'n Go :: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

TNGSB respects the right to privacy of our customers. Our privacy policy ensures that we protect the trust you place in us when you provide us with your personal information. Keeping customer information secure, and using it only as our customers would want us to, is a top priority for all of us at TNGSB. 

**TNGSB Privacy Policy  
**

1.      We will safeguard, according to strict standards of security and confidentiality, any information our customers share with us.

2.      We will limit the collection and use of customer information to the minimum as may be required to deliver superior service to our customers, which includes advising our customers about our products, services and other opportunities, and to administer our business.

3.      We will permit only authorized employees, who are trained in the proper handling of customer information, to have access to that information.

4.      Whenever we hire other organizations to provide support services, we will require them to conform to our privacy standards and to allow us to audit them for compliance.

**Collection of Personal Information  
**

The information we collect is information that we require in order to perform our services and offer our products to you. This information is similar to the information typically collected by us on the application forms, which include, but not limited to, your name and address details, date of birth, details such as telephone number and others.  

You may choose to give us personal information directly in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to give us your name and contact information to communicate with you to register for a service, to provide you with a subscription, or to do business with us if you are a supplier or business affiliate/alliance. If you inform us that you do not want us to use your information to make further contact with you beyond fulfilling your request, we will respect your wishes.  

From time to time, we may also collect information that pertains to you indirectly through other sources (if any). When we do so, we require the third party to confirm that the information was legally acquired by them and that we have the right to obtain it from them and use it. The information that we collect, either directly or indirectly, may be combined to help us improve its overall accuracy and completeness and to help us better tailor our interactions with you. 

**Use of Personal Information**

Fulfilling your Transaction Request

If you request something from TNGSB, for example, a product or service, we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share information with others, for instance, TNGSB's business partners, TNGSB’s related and/or affiliated company and financial institutions involved in fulfillment. In connection with a transaction, we may also contact you as part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes.

Personalizing your Experience on our Web Sites

We may use information we collect about you to provide you with a personalized experience on our Web sites, such as providing you with content in which you may be interested and making navigation on our sites easier.

Marketing

The information you provide to TNGSB, as well as the information we have collected about you indirectly, may be used by TNGSB for marketing purposes. Before we do so, however, we will offer you the opportunity to choose whether or not to have your information used in this way. You may at any time choose not to receive marketing materials from us by contacting us directly (please refer to “Questions and Concern” below).  

Some of our offerings may be co-branded, that is sponsored by both TNGSB and third parties. If you sign up for these offerings, be aware that your information may also be collected by and shared with those third parties. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with their privacy policies to gain an understanding of the manner in which they will handle information about you.  If you choose to “Email This Page” to a friend or colleague, we will ask for their name and e-mail address. We will automatically send a one-time e-mail sharing the page you indicated, but will not use that information for other purposes.

Recruitment

In connection with a job application or inquiry, whether advertised on TNGSB Web site or otherwise, you may provide us with information about yourself, such as a resume. We may use this information throughout TNGSB in order to address your inquiry or consider you for employment purposes.

Protect the Rights and Property of TNGSB and Others

We may also use or share your information to protect the rights or property of TNGSB, our business partners, suppliers, clients, or others when we have reasonable grounds to believe that such rights or property have been or could be affected. In addition, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, or the rights of others, or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web sites.

Information for Business Partners

If you represent TNGSB’s business partner, you may visit TNGSB Web sites intended specifically for TNGSB’s business partners. We may use information provided on that site to administer and develop our business relationship with you, the business partner you represent, and TNGSB business partners generally. For instance, this may involve using your information to send you details of TNGSB’s business partner programs. It may also include sharing certain information with other business partners (subject to any confidentiality obligations that may exist), or TNGSB customers or prospects. In connection with a particular transaction or program, we may also contact you as part of customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes.

Information for Suppliers 

If you represent TNGSB’s supplier, you may visit TNGSB Web sites intended specifically for use by TNGSB’s suppliers. We may use the information provided on that site in connection with entering into or performing a transaction with you. For example, this may include sharing information with other parts of TNGSB, TNGSB's business partners, customers, shipping companies, financial institutions and postal or government authorities involved in fulfillment. It may also be used to administer and develop our relationship with you, the supplier you represent, and other TNGSB’s suppliers generally.

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**

We also collect non-personal information/data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  1. We may collect information such as occupation, language, postcode, area code, unique device identifier, location and the time zone where the TNGSB products or services are used, so that we can better understand customer behaviour and improve our products, services and advertising.
  2. We also may collect information regarding customer activities on our website and from our other products and services. This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website, products and services are of most interest. Aggregated data is considered non-personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Statement.

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

**Disclosure of Information**

TNGSB complies with the data protection laws in Malaysia and takes all reasonable care to prevent any unauthorized access to your personal data. TNGSB and those working for agents or contractors of TNGSB have the responsibility to keep your information confidential and will only use it to offer products and services on behalf of TNGSB.

**Disclosure to Third Parties**

At times TNGSB may make certain personal information available to strategic affiliates/alliances that work with TNGSB to provide products and services, or that help TNGSB market to customers. 

Service Providers

TNGSB shares personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever TNGSB operates.

Others

It may be necessary — by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence, for TNGSB to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement or other issues of public importance — disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users.  Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger or sale, we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

**Information Security and Accuracy  
**

TNGSB takes precautions including administrative, technical and physical measures to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft and misuse, as well as against unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.  Furthermore, we intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its accuracy. TNGSB implements reasonable physical, administrative and technical safeguards to help us protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure.

Email addresses

At TNGSB we respect the privacy of personal email accounts and we store your email addresses just as securely as other personal information on our website.  We will not send you unwanted email messages or junk mail, and your details will not be passed to any organization which is not related to TNGSB or its group of companies without your permission.

**Sharing of Personal Information  
**

From time to time, we may disclose information that identifies you at an individual level and which we collected on our Web sites to other non-TNGSB entities that are not acting as our suppliers, such as our business partners.  Except as described in this Privacy Statement, we will only do so with your prior consent. We do not sell or lease such information.    

Please be aware that in certain circumstances, personal information may be subject to disclosure to government agencies pursuant to judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. We may also share your information to protect the rights or property of TNGSB, our business partners, suppliers or clients, and others when we have reasonable grounds to believe that such rights or property have been or could be affected.

**Integrity and Retention of Personal Information**

TNGSB makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete and up to date. We will retain your personal information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to request that we no longer use your registration information to provide you services contact us at [careline@touchngo.com.my](mailto:careline@touchngo.com.my). We will retain and use your registration information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Access and Correction to Personal Information**

For other personal information, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if TNGSB is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests if no information is supplied to prove your identity, no information is supplied to locate the personal data, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy or confidential information of others, or for which access is in violation of the law. Access, correction or deletion requests can be made by contacting TOUCH ‘N GO Careline at +603-2714 8888 or you can visit the nearest TOUCH ‘N GO Service Centres and/or Hubs if you would like to make any enquiries or complaints or request access or correction of your personal information.  Any request of access of correction of personal data may be subjected to any privacy or data protection laws.

**Third-Party Sites and Services**

TNGSB websites, products, applications and services may contain links to third-party websites, products and services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties.  Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details are governed by their privacy practices. This means, third party internet sites that you can link through TNGSB are not covered by our policy. Therefore, we encourage you to familiarize with those third parties sites’ privacy policies before using the links or applications and we urge you to be careful when you enter any personal information online.  TNGSB accepts no responsibility or liability for those sites.

**Use of Cookies**

Our website creates a “cookie” when you first register online. A “cookie” is a piece of information, like a tag, which some basic information which helps us to identify if you have visited the site before and if you have provide us with some personalized content such as welcoming you by name if you have supplied this in a previous visit.  However, as it is based on your PC, we will not find the “cookie” if you visit our website from a different PC to the one you registered on.  The use of “cookies” includes the following assurances:

No information regarding your telephone number, an account or payment details included in the cookie or can be accessed using it;

They do not collect any personal information regarding the use of your PC or internet browsing in any way;

If you do not want a “cookie” to be created on your PC, web browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox of Google Chrome provide the option to disable them.  Please bear in mind that some personalized services on website may not be available if you choose to disable cookies.

TNGSB also uses third parties to track its advertising across the web.  The information these third parties collect does not include any personal information, but is merely for the purpose of identifying the general effectiveness of such online advertising.

**Our Companywide Commitment to Your Privacy**

To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to TNGSB employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

TNGSB may review and update its Privacy Statement from time to time to reflect changes in the law, changes in our business practices, procedures and structure, and the community’s changing privacy expectations. While it is not generally feasible to notify you of any changes to this policy, the latest version of the policy may be available on TNGSB’s website to obtain the latest version of the Privacy Statement at any time.

**Questions or Concerns**

If you have any question or concern, please call TOUCH ‘N GO Careline at +603-2714 8888 or e-mail at [careline@touchngo.com.my](mailto:careline@touchngo.com.my) ****
